Guide to the Dale R. Corson papers, 1963-1977
Corson, Dale R. papers, 1963-1977
- Series I. Administrative Papers
  - 1975-1976
    - Study of Institutional Priorities - Task Force 1 22, Life Safety, Safety Division, Traffic, Parking, Campus Bus., 1975 (Box 115, Folder 9-10)
    - Study of Institutional Priorities - Task Force 1 23, University Unions., 1975 (Box 115, Folder 11-12)
    - Study of Institutional Priorities - Task Force 1 24, Utilization of User Charges., 1975-76 (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Study of Institutional Priorities - Task Force 1 25, Developing Austerity in Community Behavior., 1975 (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Study of Institutional Priorities - Task Force 1 26, Public Affairs., 1975-76 (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Study of Institutional Priorities - Task Force 1 27, Athletics and Physical Education., 1975 (Box 115, Folder 16-17)
    - Emeritus Professors, Correspondence., 1967-74 (Box 115, Folder 18-28)
      Congratulatory letters from DRC.
  - 1976-1977
    - President., 1976 (Box 115, Folder 29)
      Musick, Jack; Dean, Arthur H.; Miller, Robert D.; Hill, Albert G.; Culler, Jonathan; Mizener, Arthur M.; Brown, Maynard.
    - President., 1976-77 (Box 115, Folder 30)
      Monahan, Edward C.; Malott, Deane W.
    - President., 1977 (Box 115, Folder 31)
      Sevilla, Elena; Gottfried, Kurt; Farrell, Robert T.
    - President., 1977 (Box 115, Folder 32)
      Sevilla, Elena.
    - Dale R. Corson - Change of Status., 1976-77 (Box 115, Folder 33)
      Clark, John M.; Requardt, Gustav J.; Muka, Betty O.; Grasselli, Caesar A.; McConkey, James R.; Vinik, Tolly; Purcell, Robert W.
    - Dale R. Corson - Change of Status., 1977 (Box 115, Folder 34)
    - Invitations., 1976-77 (Box 115, Folder 35)
    - Invitations - Regrets., 1976-77 (Box 115, Folder 36-41)
    - Presidential Councillors., 1975-76 (Box 115, Folder 42)
      Carpenter, Walter S.; Linowitz, Sol M.; Dean, Arthur H.; Newbury, George A. Letter from DRC to Councillors.
    - Presidential Councillors., 1976-77 (Box 115, Folder 43)
      Center for the Study of the Private Enterprise System (Proposed).
    - Presidential Councillors., 1977 (Box 115, Folder 44)
      Stevens, Stoddard M.; 01 in, John M.
    - Sel f -Governance., 1977 (Box 115, Folder 45)
      Committee to Review the Judicial System.
    - Self -Governance., 1977 (Box 115, Folder 46)
    - Sel f -Governance., 1976 (Box 115, Folder 47)
      Chester, Geoffrey V.; Cooke, W. Donald. Commission on Self -Governance.
    - Sel f -Governance., 1976-77 (Box 115, Folder 48)
      Chester, Geoffrey V.; Gurowitz, William D. Commission on Self -Governance.
    - Sel f -Governance., 1977 (Box 115, Folder 49)
      Chester, Geoffrey V.; Noden, Malcolm A. Commission on Self -Governance 7 Campus referendum on self -governance.
    - Sel f -Governance., 1977 (Box 115, Folder 50)
      Chester, Geoffrey V.; Noden, Malcolm A.; McDonald, Robert J.; Lake, Charles W. Commission on Self -Governance; Campus referendum on self -governance.
    - Sel f -Governance., 1977 (Box 116, Folder 1)
      Chester, Geoffrey V.; Rakov, Elizabeth R.; Flansburgh, E. Schuyler; Saunders, Byron W. Commission on Self -Governance; Campus referendum on self -governance; "An Alternative Self -Governance Proposal."
    - Sel f -Governance., 1977 (Box 116, Folder 2)
      Chester, Geoffrey V.; Saunders, Byron W.; Wolfe, Hawley L.; Merkelson, Wayne P.
    - Sel f -Governance., 1977 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Sel f -Governance., 1977 (Box 116, Folder 4)
      Chester, Geoffrey V.; Gurowitz, William D.; Rhodes, Frank H. T. Commission on Self -Governance.
    - Sel f -Governance. Chester, Geoffrey V.; Lake, Charles W.; Stamp, Neal R. Campus referendum on self -governance., 1977 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Study Commission on Self -Governance., 1976 (Box 116, Folder 6)
      Chester, Geoffrey V.; Stein, Peter; Robert; Gurowitz, William D.; Stamp, Neal R. University Senate.
    - Study commission on self -Governance., 1976 (Box 116, Folder 7)
      Chester, Geoffrey V.; Miller, Robert D.
    - Study Commission on self -Governance., 1976 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Study Commission on Self -Governance., 1976 (Box 116, Folder 9)
      Chester, Geoffrey V.; Wolfe, Hawley L. Commission on Self -Governance; University Senate Study Group.
    - Commission to Review the Campus Judicial System., 1976 (Box 116, Folder 10)
      Bugliari, Joseph B.
    - Commission to Review the Campus Judicial System., 1976 (Box 116, Folder 11)
      Bugliari, Joseph B.; Duxbury, John M.
    - Commission to Review the Campus Judicial System., 1976-77 (Box 116, Folder 12)
      Bugliari, Joseph B.; Smith, Katherine; Saunders, Byron W.
    - Assistant to the President., 1976-77 (Box 116, Folder 13-15)
      Barlow, J. Robert. Commission on Self -Governance.
    - Office of the Provost., 1975 (Box 116, Folder 16)
      Knapp, David C.; Rivera, Ramon E. "Report on the Minority Graduate Program. "
    - Office of the Provost., 1976-77 (Box 116, Folder 17)
      Knapp, David C.; Osby, William J. American Council on Education.
    - Provost's Committees., 1976-77 (Box 116, Folder 18)
      Knapp, David C.; Roscoe, Ann F. Committee on the Status of Women; Cornell Classification Plan; Affirmative Action Advisory Board; Affirmative action.
    - Affirmative Action., 1976-77 (Box 116, Folder 19)
      Rivera, Ramon E.; Murray, Connie. Affirmative Action Program; Women's Caucus.
    - Affirmative Action., 1976 (Box 116, Folder 20)
      Cooke, W. Donald. United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare; "Information on the Availability of Minorities and Women for Academic Appointments. "
    - Affirmative Action., 1976-77 (Box 116, Folder 21)
      Knapp, David C.; Rivera, Ramon E. Affirmative Action Program.
    - Affirmative Action., 1975-77 (Box 116, Folder 22)
      Rivera, Ramon E.; Cooke, w. Donald.
    - Affirmative Action - Civil Rights Cases., 1976-77 (Box 116, Folder 23)
      Wolf son, Michael I.; Parker, Herbert; Hoffman, Neal M.
    - Affirmative Action - Civil Rights Cases., 1976-77 (Box 116, Folder 24)
      Glasse, Antonia; Lee, D. Boardman; Ameen, Syed.
    - Affirmative Action - Civil Rights Cases., 1976-77 (Box 116, Folder 25)
      Ezergailis, Inta Miske; Knapp, David C.; Wolf son, Michael I.; Glasse, Antonia.
    - Affirmative Action - Civil Rights Cases., 1976-77 (Box 116, Folder 26)
      Boyd, Susan I.; Wolf son, Michael I.; Ezergailis, Inta Miske; Levin, Harry.
    - Division of Biological Sciences., 1976-77 (Box 116, Folder 27)
      Kennedy, W. Keith. Pew Charitable Trust; Liberty Hyde Bailey Hortorium; Ford Foundation.
    - Division of Biological Sciences., 1976-77 (Box 116, Folder 28)
      O'Brien, Richard D.; Wu, Ray. Wing Hall; Lower Alumni Field.
    - Center for the Study of the American Political Economy (Proposed)., 1976-77 (Box 116, Folder 29)
      Maynes, E. Scott; Hildebrand, George H.; Olin, John M.; Levin, Harry; O'Connell, Francis A.; Knapp, David C. Committee on Academic Programs and Policies.
    - Cornell University Libraries., 1976-77 (Box 116, Folder 30)
      Miller, J. Gormly; Dean, Arthur H. Andrew W. Mellon Foundation; Research Libraries Group. Houdon bust of Lafayette.
    - College of Arts and Sciences., 1976 (Box 116, Folder 31)
      Levin, Harry; Knapp, David C.; Kahn, Alfred E. Committee on General Education.
    - College of Arts and Sciences., 1977 (Box 116, Folder 32)
      Levin, Harry; Harwit, Martin 0.; Kahn, Alfred E. Outside offers to faculty.
    - College of Arts and Sciences., 1977 (Box 116, Folder 33)
      Levin, Harry; Knapp, David C.; Klein, Richard; Grossvogel, David I. Whiton Fund; Committee on the Training of Teaching Assistants; Committee to Reward Excellent Teaching.
    - Computing., 1976-77 (Box 116, Folder 34)
      Cranch, E. T.; Rudan, John W.; Lawrence, Samuel A. Office of Computer Services; Computing Board.
    - Lafayette Papers., 1977 (Box 116, Folder 35)
      Howley, Roger; Kosciusko-Morizet, Jacques; Finch, C. Herbert; Rhodes, Frank H. T.; Linowitz, Sol M.; Souchet, Dominique.
    - Lafayette Papers., 1978 (Box 116, Folder 36)
      Handlan, Scharlie B.; Nosanow, Barbara S.; Idzerda, Stanley J.
    - Africana Studies and Research Center., 1975-76 (Box 116, Folder 37)
      Gurowitz, William D.; Lambert, William W.; Eberts, Paul; Knapp, David C.; Bowers, Raymond. Bus service; Committee to Review the Africana Studies and Research Center.
    - CO8EP., 1975-77 (Box 116, Folder 38-40)
      Barlow, Mark; Cross, Dawn M.; Williams, Darwin.
    - Ethnic Studies., 1972-77 (Box 116, Folder 41)
      Diaz, Noe; Hataye, Michael K. New Coalition; Coalition of Minority Students.
    - Higher Education Opportunity Program -Educational Opportunity Program (HEOP-EOP)., 1974-77 (Box 116, Folder 42-43)
    - Minority Education., 1976 (Box 116, Folder 44)
      Fessenden-Raden, June M.; Parsons, Kermit C. Office of Minority Affairs.
    - Minority Education., 1976-77 (Box 116, Folder 45)
      Richardson, Henry W. Asian American students.
    - Minority Education., 1977 (Box 116, Folder 46)
      Hoffman, Roald; Williams, Darwin; Collins, William. Committee on the Status of Minorities.
    - Native Americans., 1975-77 (Box 116, Folder 47)
      Abrams, Barbara; Graham, Donald C.; Dickason, Donald G.; Jones, William D. Native American Program.
    - Office of Admissions., 1976 (Box 116, Folder 48)
      Barlow, Mark; Dickason, Donald G.
    - Financial Aid., 1976-77 (Box 116, Folder 49)
    - Herbert F. Johnson Museum of Art., 1976-77 (Box 116, Folder 50)
      Leavitt, Thomas W.
    - Andrew Dickson White Professors-at-large. Black, Max., 1976-77 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Student Support services., 1976-77 (Box 117, Folder 2-3)
      Committee on Student Development Support.
    - Salary Recovery Research Costs. Cooke, W. Donald., 1975-76 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Center for International studies. Esman, Milton J.; Pintner, Walter M.; Reischauer, Edwin 0.; WardJ Robert. Committee on Soviet Studies., 1976-77 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - COSEP - Historical Material., 1969-70 (Box 117, Folder 6)
      Scott, Robert A.; Jones, William D.; Knapp, David C.; Miller, Frank B.
    - COSEP - Historical Material., 1970 (Box 117, Folder 7)
      Carr, Carson; Carter, Lisle: C. Minority education.
    - COSEP - Historical Material., 1970 (Box 117, Folder 8)
      Jones, William D.; Knapp, Eiavid C.; Gaffney, Margaret; Barlow, Mark. COSEP admissions and recruitment.
    - COSEP - Historical Material., 1970 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - COSEP - Historical Material., 1970 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - COSEP - Historical Material., 1970-71 (Box 117, Folder 11)
      Pape, Helen. Division of Educational Opportunity.
    - COSEP - Historical Material., 1970-71 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - COSEP - Historical Material., 1971-72 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - COSEP - Historical Material., 1973-74 (Box 117, Folder 14)
      New Coalition.
    - COSEP - Historical Material. Lee, Gary A. COSEP financial aid guidelines., 1970 (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - COSEP - Historical Material., 1971 (Box 117, Folder 16)
      Lee, Gary A. COSEP financial aid guidelines; Agreement between the college deans and COSEP.
    - C08EP - Historical Material., 1972-74 (Box 117, Folder 17)
      Lee, Gary A.; Failing, Jean. COSEP financial aid guidelines; Agreement between the college deans and COSEP; Educational Opportunity Program.
    - COSEP - Historical Material. Plane, Robert A. COSEP Committee., 1969-70 (Box 117, Folder 18)
    - COSEP - Historical Material. Cannady, Charisse A. COSEP Student Handbook; COSEP Committee., 1970-71 (Box 117, Folder 19)
    - COSEP - Historical Material., 1971 (Box 117, Folder 20)
      Plane, Robert A. COSEP Student Handbook; Committee to Review the COSEP Handbook.
    - COSEP - Historical Material. Santiago, Letty; Mosley, Mary S. COSEP Handbook., 1971-74 (Box 117, Folder 21)
    - Office of the Judicial Administrator. Cohen, Calvin J.; Nichols, Benjamin; Gurowitz, William D.; Kauber, Barbara M.; Harmon, Joseph A.; Wheeler, Thomas., 1974-75 (Box 117, Folder 22)
    - Office of the Judicial Administrator. Kauber, Barbara M.; Knapp, David C.; Smith, Katherine. "Violations and Penalties in the Campus Judicial System.11, 1976-77 (Box 117, Folder 23)
    - Office of the Judicial Administrator. Kauber, Barbara M., 1977 (Box 117, Folder 24)
    - Judicial Advisor., 1975 (Box 117, Folder 25)
      Provine, William.
    - Judicial Advisor., 1975-77 (Box 117, Folder 26)
      Kauber, Barbara M.; Ma thews, Isiah C.
    - Office of the University Ombudsman., 1971-73 (Box 117, Folder 27)
      Danelski, David J.; Hart, Joycelyn; Bricker, Ronald A.
    - Office of the University Ombudsman., 1975 (Box 117, Folder 28)
      Miller, Robert D.; Greisen, Kenneth I.
    - Office of the University Ombudsman. Bricker, Ronald A., 1975-77 (Box 117, Folder 29)
    - Judicial Boards., 1973-77 (Box 117, Folder 30)
      Hearing Board; Review Board.
    - Senior Vice President., 1976-77 (Box 117, Folder 31)
      Herbster, William G.; Guerlac, Henry. Esso Education Foundation.
    - Office of Personnel Services. Nagel, Claire M.; Herbster, William G., 1976 (Box 117, Folder 32)
    - Office of Personnel Services., 1976-77 (Box 117, Folder 33)
      Willers, Diedrich K.; Herbster, William G.
    - Office of Personnel Services., 1977 (Box 117, Folder 34)
      Herbster, William G.
    - Office of Personnel Services - Collective Bargaining., 1976-77 (Box 117, Folder 35)
      Civil Service Employees Association; Teamsters.
    - Office of Personnel Services - Degree Programs for University Staff., 1976-77 (Box 117, Folder 36)
      Haskins, Jacquelyn L.
    - Office of Personnel Services - Fringe Benefits., 1974-76 (Box 117, Folder 37)
      Ruoff, Arthur L.; Lawrence, Samuel A.
    - Office of Personnel services - Fringe Benefits., 1976 (Box 117, Folder 38-39)
    - Office of Personnel Services - Fringe Benefits., 1976 (Box 117, Folder 40)
      Saunders, Byron W.; McConnell, John W.
    - Office of Personnel Services - Fringe Benefits., 1976-77 (Box 117, Folder 41)
    - Office of Personnel Services - Fringe Benefits., 1977 (Box 117, Folder 42)
    - Office of Personnel Services - Middle Management., 1976-77 (Box 117, Folder 43)
    - Office of Personnel Services - Personnel Data. Nagel, Claire M., 1977 (Box 117, Folder 44)
    - Office of Personnel Services - Personnel Planning and Policy Board., 1976-77 (Box 117, Folder 45)
    - Office of Personnel Services - Personnel Policies and Procedures., 1975-76 (Box 117, Folder 46)
    - Personnel Salary Study., 9 1974 (Box 117, Folder 47-4!)
      Elliott, Nancy; Willers, Diedrich K.; Storandt, Robert W.
    - Department of Physical Education and Athletics., 1975-76 (Box 117, Folder 50)
      Gurowitz, William D.; Jenkins, William A. Committee on the Status of Minorities; Board of Trustees - Committee on Athletics.
    - Department of Physical Education and Athletics., 1976 (Box 117, Folder 51)
      Abrams, Meyer H.; Gurowitz, William D.
    - Department of Physical Education and Athletics., 1976 (Box 117, Folder 52)
      Abrams, Meyer H.; Schultz, Richard D.; Gurowitz, William D.; Schaenen, Nelson; Kennedy, Laing; Smoyer, David B.; Jenkins, William A.; Matte, Thomas R.; Harter, Richard A.
    - Department of Physical Education and Athletics., 1976 (Box 117, Folder 53)
      Mestres, Ricardo A.; Grohmann, H. Victor; Schultz, Richard D.; Engel, Robert G. University of Iowa.
    - Department of Physical Education and Athletics., 1976 (Box 117, Folder 54)
      Collyer, John L.; Bluitt, Ben; Grohmann, H. Victor; Noyes, Jansen; Malott, Deane W. Collyer Boathouse.
    - Department of Physical Education and Athletics., 1976 (Box 118, Folder 1)
      Gurowitz, William D.; Herbster, William G.; Schultz, Richard D.; Bluitt, Ben; Jenkins, William A.; Kane, Robert J. Lynah Rink.
    - Department of Physical Education and Athletics., 1976 (Box 118, Folder 2)
      Seifert, George G.; Schultz, Richard D.
    - Department of Physical Education and Athletics., 1976-77 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      Schultz, Richard D.; Blackman, Robert.
    - Department of Physical Education and Athletics., 1974-77 (Box 118, Folder 4)
      Bluitt, Ben; Schultz, Richard D. National Junior Olympics.
    - Department of Physical Education and Athletics., 1975 (Box 118, Folder 5)
      Musick, Jack; Gurowitz, William D.
    - Department of Physical Education and Athletics., 1975-76 (Box 118, Folder 6)
      Schaenen, Nelson; Robison, Ell is H.
    - Department of Physical Education and Athletics., 1976-77 (Box 118, Folder 7)
      Neimeth, Albert C.
    - Department of Physical Education and Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association., 1975-76 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Department of Physical Education and Athletics - National Collegiate Athletic Association., 1976-77 (Box 118, Folder 9)
      Fuzak, John A.
    - Salaries - General., 1976-77 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Office of the University Counsel., 1972-73 (Box 118, Folder 11)
      Stamp, Neal R.; Dunham, Richard L.
    - Office of the University Counsel. Stamp, Neal R.; Lawrence, Samuel A.; Gurowitz, William D.; Baker, Ross Lee., 1974-75 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Office of the University Counsel., 1975 (Box 118, Folder 13)
      Stamp, Neal R.; Riggs, Barbara S.; Riggs, Henderson G.; Lindstron, Suzanne J.; Anderson, Ezra D.
    - Office of the University Counsel., 1975-76 (Box 118, Folder 14)
      Stamp, Neal R.; Carmichael, Calum; Riggs, Henderson G. Ivy League Lawyers' Consortium.
    - Office of the University Counsel., 1976 (Box 118, Folder 15)
      Stamp, Neal R.; Riggs, Henderson G.
    - Office of the University Counsel., 1977 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - Vice President for Financial and Planning Services (Vice President for Administration)., 1975-76 (Box 118, Folder 17)
      Lawrence, Samuel A. Administrative Council.
    - Vice President for Financial and Planning Services (Vice President for Administration)., 1976-77 (Box 118, Folder 18)
      Lawrence, Samuel A.; Stewart, lan R.
    - Vice President for Financial and Planning Services (Vice President for Administration)., 1977 (Box 118, Folder 19-20)
      Lawrence, Samuel A.; Herbster, William G.
    - Budget 1976-77., 1975-77 (Box 118, Folder 21-28)
    - Budget Discussion Papers., 1976-77 (Box 118, Folder 29)
    - Five Year Financial Resource Analysis., 1974-77 (Box 118, Folder 30-33)
    - Bursar* s Office., 1975-77 (Box 118, Folder 34)
      Lyon, James F.
    - Institutional Information - Division of Management Systems and Analysis., 1976-77 (Box 118, Folder 35-37)
    - Division of Management Systems and Analysis - Miscellaneous Analyses., 1974-76 (Box 118, Folder 38-42)
    - Payroll System., 1976-77 (Box 118, Folder 43)
    - Student Information System., 1975 (Box 118, Folder 44)
      Information Associates, Inc.
    - Stanford University Budget Papers., 1973-74 (Box 118, Folder 45-46)
    - Responsibility Centers Analysis., 1975-76 (Box 118, Folder 47-50)
      Lawrence, Samuel A.; Ostrom, John S. Financial Systems Development.
    - Office of the Treasurer and Chief Fiscal Officer., 1976 (Box 118, Folder 51)
      Peterson, Arthur H.; Collyer, John L.; Will, Philip. Testimonial letters to AHP.
    - Office of the Treasurer and Chief Fiscal Officer., 1976 (Box 119, Folder 1-2)
      Peterson, Arthur H. Testimonial letters to AHP.
    - Office of the Treasurer and Vice President., 1975-77 (Box 119, Folder 3-4)
      Horn, Robert T.
    - Laboratory of ornithology. Lancaster, Douglas A., 1975-77 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - WHCU., 1972-77 (Box 119, Folder 6)
      Deal, Jack; Reaves, Stanford. Department of Black Affairs.
    - Cornell Aeronautical Laboratory - Calspan Corporation., 1976-77 (Box 119, Folder 7)
      Moffitt, Henry K.
    - Vice President for Campus Affairs., 1976 (Box 119, Folder S)
      Gurowitz, William D.; Ryan, Elizabeth; Pierce, Samuel R. Committee on Hunger.
    - Vice President for Campus Affairs. Gurowitz, William D. Coordinating Committee on the World Food Situation., 1977 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Campus Store., 1976 (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Center for the Study of Religion, Ethics, and Social Policy (CRESP)., 1976 (Box 119, Folder 11)
      Lewis, W. Jack. Sage Chapel; Office of Religious Affairs.
    - Center for the Study of Religion, Ethics, and Social Policy (CRESP)., 1976-77 (Box 119, Folder 12)
      Lewis, W. Jack; Gurowitz, William D. Reorganization of religious affairs at Cornell University.
    - Conference Coordinator., 1976-77 (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - Dean of Students., 1976 (Box 119, Folder 14-1£)
    - Dean of Students., 1977 (Box 119, Folder 16)
      Meyer, Elmer E.; Neel, Benjamin.
    - Department of Dining Services., 1976-77 (Box 119, Folder 17)
      Fischer, Richard B.; Silber, John R.
    - Department of Student Housing., 1976-77 (Box 119, Folder 18)
      Paleen, William P.
    - Inter religious International Ministry., 1977 (Box 119, Folder 19)
    - International Student Office., 1976-77 (Box 119, Folder 20)
      Williams, David B.; Rushdy, Sherif; Thayer, Jira Payne.
    - Career Center., 1976-77 (Box 119, Folder 21)
      Ottinger, Richard L.
    - Safety Division (Department of Public Safety) - Building and Key Security., 1975-76 (Box 119, Folder 22)
    - Safety Division (Department of Public Safety)., 1974-75 (Box 119, Folder 23)
      McDaniel, William E.; Brown, David W. Parking.
    - Safety Division (Department of Public Safety). Rape; Security Lighting Program., 1976 (Box 119, Folder 24)
    - Safety Division (Department of Public Safety). Blue Light phones and lighting, 1977 (Box 119, Folder 25)
    - Safety Division - Monthly Management Report., 1975-76 (Box 119, Folder 26-28)
    - Safety Division (Department of Public Safety) - Personnel., 1975 (Box 119, Folder 29)
    - Safety Division (Department of Public Safety) - Photo Policy., 1976-70 (Box 119, Folder 30)
    - Safety Division (Department of Public Safety) - Policies., 1977 (Box 119, Folder 31)
    - Safety Division (Department of Public Safety) - Supervisory Training Program., 1971-74 (Box 119, Folder 32)
    - Transportation Services., 1970-76 (Box 119, Folder 33)
      Brown, David W.; Turner, James E.; Haskins, Jacquelyn L. Bus service to Africana Studies and Research Center; Parking at Langmuir Laboratory.
    - Transportation Services., 1976-77 (Box 119, Folder 34)
      Richards, William H.; Merrill, Robert P.; Brown, David W.
    - University Health Services., 1976-77 (Box 119, Folder 35)
    - Cornell University Health Care Plan., 1976 (Box 119, Folder 36)
    - University Health Services - New Center., 1976-77 (Box 119, Folder 37)
      Gurowitz, William D.; Levin, Harry. Gannett Foundation; Tompkins County Health Services Alliance.
    - New Tompkins County Hospital., 1976 (Box 119, Folder 38)
      Gurowitz, William D.; Nissenson, Leonard.
    - Department of University Unions., 1977 (Box 119, Folder 39)
    - Vice President for Facilities and Business Operations., 1975 (Box 119, Folder 40)
      Lawrence, Samuel A.; Knapp, David C.
    - Vice President for Facilities and Business Operations., 1975-76 (Box 119, Folder 41)
      Fane, Jason H. Langmuir Laboratory.
    - Vice President for Facilities and Business Operations., 1976-77 (Box 119, Folder 42)
    - Cornell Plantations. Lewis, Richard M.; Palm, Charles E.; Hugo-Brunt, Michael., 1975-76 (Box 119, Folder 43)
    - Critical Maintenance., 1976-77 (Box 119, Folder 44-46)
    - Energy Conservation., 1976-77 (Box 119, Folder 47-48)
      Gurowitz, William D.; Kahn, Alfred E.; Pooler, Rosemary S.
    - Department of General Services., 1976-77 (Box 119, Folder 49)
      Lee, Gary A.; Rogers, Wallace B.
    - Travel Office., 1976 (Box 119, Folder 50)
      McHugh, Matthew F.
    - Life Safety Services., 1976-77 (Box 119, Folder 51)
    - Real Estate Department, 1973-77 (Box 119, Folder 52)